On Sunday the 22nd of May 2016, during The SCOAN Live Sunday Service,
Prophet T.B. Joshua revealed a prophetic message regarding the United Kingdom
and called on them to pray for the nation.
These were his words…
In Jesus' mighty name we pray.
[Amen.]
Like I was saying, one of the issues I must talk about - they should pray for the United Kingdom -
because I am seeing some funny people in their country.
So, they should pray for them - the United Kingdom.
But I am seeing with prayer and their proper security, it will be aborted.
But there will be a sign and there will be a trace that this happened.
It will not happen the way it was supposed to have happened.
But they will know something happened there.
They have to pray with proper security.
Funny people are there as I am talking now.
So, raise your voice and pray for the nation.
Innocent soul.
UK TERROR ATTACK!!! | TB Joshua Prophecy
Step into the future.
Be the first to know.
Find out what God has to say concerning your situation, your country, and the world.
God is still saying something.
A compilation of prophecies concerning individuals, nations, and the world at large
together with confirmations.
I am seeing flame. What is the meaning of that?
A prophet of God shall say that what he shall live to see accomplished.
In every situation God has something to say.
Find out what God has to say
God is still saying something.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from the Synagogue Church of all Nations
Emmanuel TV – Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 03/07/2018